You're not here
to gloat, are you?
I practically saved
your life.
Is that how you speak to me?
Saved my life?
Focus the camera.
Something's wrong with Xia Yimo.
Is she drowning?
No way.
Isn't Ms. Xia a good swimmer?
Exactly.
No,
save them!
Wait, who knows how to dive?
Hurry up!
Who can do it? Hurry!
Help!
Hurry!
Been in a coma for days
and remembers nothing.
Still acting tough
about your swimming skills.
What's wrong?
When I was in a coma,
I felt like I had a very long dream.
In the dream,
I played many roles.
To save
Xue Ruowan, the role you played,
I died over and over again.
I thought
you would stab me
a few times in your dream.
I'm not that dark inside.
About me accidentally
hurting you with a prop
during last year's audition,
and getting that role in the end,
have you always thought
I did it on purpose?
I know
you didn't tamper with the prop.
Director,
I told you about this before.
Ms. Xiaofei,
Her acting is really good.
Hello, Director.
Hello.
You're just in time.
Can you two do a scene together?
Ms. Xia will play the older sister,
and Ms. Sun the younger sister.
I don't want to fight with you.
I just want to live my life.
Anyway...
If you dare take a step today,
I'll kill you.
Momo,
Who prepared the props?
Where are they?
I terminated my contract back then
because everyone gave
all the resources to you
and treated me as a foil.
I was just a nobody
that no one cared about.
Even though I know
you've always helped me...
But in my eyes at the time,
it was just charity.
I never treated you
as my foil.
I did all this
just so you wouldn't end up like me,
after getting famous,
losing the right to choose
and taking repetitive roles.
That's why I kept fighting
for those roles for you,
but I ignored your feelings.
It was my fault.
It's all in the past.
So,
are we still friends?
Of course.
However...
I saw people online saying
I played the victim
to smear you for top billing.
Now you're definitely the female lead.
The director cast you as Xue Keying
because he truly thinks you're a good fit.
If you care so much
about this leading role,
let's compete fairly.
I've already heard.
The director found an actor to replace me.
Now, whether it's the female lead
or the second female lead,
it has nothing to do with me anymore.
Giving up already?
That doesn't sound like
the Xia Yimo I know.
Alright.
I'll get going then.
Get some good rest.
Thank you for saving me.
I didn't come here
to hear you say thank you.
Do you remember
what we said in college?
If we ever
got a little famous,
we'd act in a show together?
Why?
Why should my life and death
be decided by Xia Yimo?
I truly lived once
in the world of Moxiang.
The marks I left
in this world,
they should all belong to me,
not Xia Yimo.
Fictional characters
are just illusions.
No matter how well you act,
you're still just a character.
A fleeting dream.
No.
Every character
has their own independent life.
Now that I, Xue Keying, have been created,
don't even think about erasing me.
I want to go
here.
I'll go.
Hello?
Momo,
the public backlash is so huge.
The company and the producers of Moxiang
are about to fall out.
The boss said
you need to join
the next crew immediately.
Hello, Momo.
Can you hear me?
Okay,
I got it.
Good.
Xia Yimo,
have you forgotten your
bold words?
You said you wanted to find
your original passion for acting,
to fully immerse yourself in a role
and live for it once.
But...
They say I can't even play you well.
Once I play the second female lead,
I'll be labeled as a villainess.
What's there to be afraid of?
Do you think
you lack labels?
I...
You should live arrogantly
and beautifully
like me.
Show that spirit.
I won't allow you to fail.
Sun Xiaofei, are you crazy?
I finally managed
to kick Xia Yimo out,
and now you're the female lead.
Why are you fighting for a role for her?
I remember warning you
not to pull these dirty tricks
behind my back.
Don't think
I don't know what you did before.
Xia Yimo is my friend.
I don't want this.
There's only one female lead.
If you don't fight, she'll replace you.
Do you think Xia Yimo
is willing to be your supporting actress?
Who says I'm not willing?
Even if I can't play Xue Keying,
any other supporting role is fine.
I think
the role of Xiaolan is pretty good.
I can play it.
Didn't you buy
online articles to smear me
as a drama queen?
I'll show you
what a real drama queen is.
You...
Don't be afraid.
It's a prop.
It's fake.
Have you memorized your lines?
Of course.
It's very simple.
Hello, Ms. Xia.
Hello, Ms. Sun.
I'm actor Xiao Chen.
Who is this?
The second male lead.
He even saved you.
Weren't you the one who saved me?
Give me a hand.
It's my honor to save Ms. Xia.
I'm also your fan.
Instead of flattering me,
you should focus more
on acting.
Let's go.
Ms. Xia,
are you still going to act in this play?
Don't worry.
Excellent creators will always meet.
Let's go.
Look, the weather is so nice today.
We have distinguished guests today.
If people see you like this,
wouldn't it disgrace
our Duke's Residence?
Yesterday,
your precious daughter
misread the couplet
written by Her Majesty
at the spring banquet.
Why didn't you say
she disgraced the Duke's Residence?
You loser,
how dare you laugh at my daughter?
See how I'll teach you a lesson today.
My dear,
why are you sleeping here?
Ying'er!
Wake up.
Mother.
Come, get up.
Slowly.
Come.
Where are we?
Are you still half-asleep?
This is our home.
By the way,
an honored guest is coming today.
Let Mother help you get ready.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
My Lady, let's go quickly.
Am I...
back again?
Ning Yuanci!
Who are you?
How dare you address me by my name?
I...